---
http_interactions:
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://opentdb.com/api.php?amount=10&category=9&difficulty=easy
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers:
      Accept-Encoding:
      - gzip;q=1.0,deflate;q=0.6,identity;q=0.3
      Accept:
      - "*/*"
      User-Agent:
      - Ruby
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Date:
      - Sun, 30 Apr 2023 06:39:08 GMT
      Server:
      - Apache
      Expires:
      - Thu, 19 Nov 1981 08:52:00 GMT
      Cache-Control:
      - no-store, no-cache, must-revalidate
      Pragma:
      - no-cache
      Access-Control-Allow-Origin:
      - "*"
      Set-Cookie:
      - PHPSESSID=3c5f825608360206333c7309f9bd341e; path=/
      Upgrade:
      - h2
      Connection:
      - Upgrade
      Vary:
      - User-Agent
      Strict-Transport-Security:
      - max-age=31536000
      Transfer-Encoding:
      - chunked
      Content-Type:
      - application/json
    body:
      encoding: UTF-8
      string: '{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What
        does a funambulist walk on?","correct_answer":"A Tight Rope","incorrect_answers":["Broken
        Glass","Balls","The Moon"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What
        is the name of the Jewish New Year?","correct_answer":"Rosh Hashanah","incorrect_answers":["Elul","New
        Year","Succoss"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"How
        many colors are there in a rainbow?","correct_answer":"7","incorrect_answers":["8","9","10"]},{"category":"General
        Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"You can legally
        drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General
        Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who is depicted
        on the US hundred dollar bill?","correct_answer":"Benjamin Franklin","incorrect_answers":["George
        Washington","Abraham Lincoln","Thomas Jefferson"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What
        do the letters of the fast food chain KFC stand for?","correct_answer":"Kentucky
        Fried Chicken","incorrect_answers":["Kentucky Fresh Cheese","Kibbled Freaky
        Cow","Kiwi Food Cut"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What
        machine element is located in the center of fidget spinners?","correct_answer":"Bearings","incorrect_answers":["Axles","Gears","Belts"]},{"category":"General
        Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What is Cynophobia
        the fear of?","correct_answer":"Dogs","incorrect_answers":["Birds","Flying","Germs"]},{"category":"General
        Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who is the youngest
        person to recieve a Nobel Prize?","correct_answer":"Malala Yousafzai","incorrect_answers":["Lawrence
        Bragg","Werner Heisenberg","Yasser Arafat"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"The
        &ldquo;fairy&rdquo; type made it&rsquo;s debut in which generation of the
        Pokemon core series games?","correct_answer":"6th","incorrect_answers":["2nd","7th","4th"]}]}'
  recorded_at: Sun, 30 Apr 2023 06:39:08 GMT
recorded_with: VCR 6.1.0
